Guide to the Mary Harron Papers MSS.608
Fales Library and Special Collections
Mary Harron Papers
1939-2018
Fales Library and Special Collections
Harron, Mary
Boo-Hooray (Gallery)
MSS.608
21.52 Linear Feet in 32 manuscript boxes, 1 record carton, 2 cassette boxes, 1 small flat box, 1 oversize flat box, 1 shared media box, 3 shared card boxes, and 1 folder in a shared oversized flat box
71 VHS
5 Betacam
1 U-matic
3 Half_Inch_Video_Reel
71 audiocassettes
10 Betacam_SP
1 Video8
31.08 Gigabytes in 625 computer files
Mary Harron (1953- ) is a Canadian-born filmmaker, screenwriter, and journalist. Harron's journalism dates from primarily the 1960s-1990s, where she focused on music and culture, particularly the early punk scenes in both London and New York. In the late 1980s, Harron began her film career by writing and directing documentaries for the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC). In the 1990s, after moving to New York, she worked as a producer for the PBS show Edge, which focused on pop culture. In 1996, Harron wrote and directed her first feature film, I Shot Andy Warhol. She went on to write and direct American Psycho (2000) and The Notorious Bettie Page (2005), and direct Charlie Says (2018). As of 2025, she has continued to direct feature films, television episodes, and miniseries. The Mary Harron Papers (dated 1939-2018) consist of materials in paper, electronic, and analog audiovisual formats created and collected by Harron documenting her career as a screenwriter, filmmaker, and journalist. Materials documenting her career as a filmmaker include research materials, pre-production documentation, and production documentation (e.g., schedules, casting, scripts), as well as clippings and publications that contain reviews or served as source material. Notable projects documented in this collection include I Shot Andy Warhol, American Psycho, and The Notorious Bettie Page. The collection also documents Harron's career as a journalist, focusing on early punk music and culture reporting. Music and culture journalism is documented through notes and transcripts of interviews, interview recordings, and published writings.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Sold by Boo-Hooray on behalf of Mary Harron in December 2021, and transferred to NYU in January 2022. The accession number associated with this purchase is 2022.004. An accretion was purchased in January 2023; the accession number associated with this purchase is 2023.007. An additional accretion was sold by Boo-Hooray for Mary Harron on March 26, 2024. The accession number associated with this donation is 2024.018.
Appraisal
Off-air recordings, in both analog and digital formats, have been appraised out of the collection due to copyright limitations. These recordings include commercial music recordings, any recording from a copyrighted broadcast or cable television transmission, and local television recordings. Broadcast recordings of which Mary Harron was a producer, director, writer, or reseracher have been retained.
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged into five series, one of which has been further arranged into subseries. The series and subseries arrangement is as follows:
Series I. Personal
Series II. Journalism and Teaching
Series III. Television
Series IV. Film
Subseries IV.A. I Shot Andy Warhol
Subseries IV.B. American Psycho
Subseries IV.C. The Notorious Bettie Page
Subseries IV.D. Charlie Says
Subseries IV.E. Shorts and Documentaries
Series V. Unrealized Projects
Each series and subseries are arranged alphabetically.
Biographical Note
Mary Harron (1953- ) is a Canadian-born filmmaker, screenwriter, and journalist. Harron's journalism, which focused on music and culture, dates from primarily the 1970s-late 1980s. She often wrote about the early punk scenes in both London and New York. She was a writer for Punk magazine in the mid-1970s, served as the drama critic for The Observer in London, and served as a music critic for The Guardian and the New Statesman. In the late 1980s, Harron began her film career by writing and directing documentaries for the British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC). Additionally, she directed episodes of the British arts show The Late Show, and in the 1990s, after moving to New York, she worked as a producer for the PBS show Edge, which focused on pop culture. In 1996, Harron wrote and directed her first feature film, I Shot Andy Warhol; it received an Independent Spirit Award nomination and opened part of the Cannes Film Festival. Harron became known for her independent films, many of which focused on women and/or controversial subjects, such as pornography and explicit violence. She went on to write and direct American Psycho (2000) and The Notorious Bettie Page (2005), and direct Charlie Says (2018). She continued to direct television episodes and miniseries, including Pasadena (2002), Big Love (2006), Six Degrees (2006), The Nine (2007), and Anna Nicole (2013). As of early 2025, she has continued to direct feature films, television episodes, and miniseries.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Scope and Contents
The Mary Harron Papers (dated 1939-2018) consist of materials in paper, electronic, and analog audiovisual formats created and collected by Harron documenting her career as a screenwriter, filmmaker, and journalist. Materials documenting her career as a filmmaker include film elements (such as voiceovers, interviews, director's cuts, and network cuts) on various media in analog and digital formats. Also included is documentation for these films, such as correspondence, research files, production books, calendars, contracts, budgets, press releases, and published reviews. Films by Harron represented in this collection include I Shot Andy Warhol, American Psycho, The Notorious Bettie Page, and Charlie Says. Short films and documentaries represented in the collection include "Streatham Ice Rink" and Holding Fast. Television shows and specials directed or produced by Harron include the The Late Show, South Bank Show, Edge, Big Love, The Nine, and Anna Nicole. The collection also documents Harron's career as a journalist, focusing on early punk music and culture reporting for publications including The Guardian, Punk, and The Village Voice. Related materials consist of notes and transcripts of interviews, interview recordings, drafts and manuscripts, correspondence with publishers, and published writings. Unrealized projects are documented through screenplay drafts, manuscripts, and research materials. A small amount of personal material is included in the collection, mainly as correspondence, photographs, journals, and daily planners. All of the materials in the collection, especially those related to her feature films, documentaries (such as Holding Fast, about a Tiben Refugee Camp), television movies (such as Anna Nicole), and unrealized projects (such as "Love Affair" which focused on Ruth Kligman, who was in a relationship with Jackson Pollock) reflect Harron's continuous focus on controversial topics or, as Harron stated in 2020 in New York Magazine, topics that "bring history to light."
Source Cited
Shapiro, Lila. "In Converation: Mary Harron." New York Magazine, April 22, 2020. https://www.vulture.com/2020/04/mary-harron-american-psycho-in-conversation.html
Women motion picture producers and directors -- United States.; Motion picture producers and directors -- Canada; Screenwriters.; Music journalists; Musical criticism.; Women journalists -- United States; I shot Andy Warhol (Motion picture); American psycho (Motion picture); Notorious Bettie Page (Motion picture); Punk culture.; Punk rock music.; Boo-Hooray (Gallery); Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987; Page, Bettie; Solanas, Valerie
- Series I. Personal, 1946-2006; 2.65 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes and 1 folder in a shared oversized flat box; 145 kilobytes in 22 computer files
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes biographical and personal materials of Harron, such as school assignments, sketchbooks, journals, daily planners, photographs, and correspondence. Also included is correspondence and illustrations by her father, Don Harron, and writing by her sister, Martha.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by topic or last name.
  - Correspondence
    - Electronic Records, 1994-1998; FA_MSS_608_ER_1
    - Letters, 1972-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Daily Planners, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Don Harron -- Comics and Correspondence, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Martha Harron -- Writing and Play Program, circa 1960-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Journals and Sketchbooks, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7-8, Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Notebooks and Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, circa 1984-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
  - Resumes and Biographies
    - Electronic Records, 1994-1995; FA_MSS_608_ER_2
    - Resume, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - St. Anne's College
    - Assignments, Exams, and Notes, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 8-9, Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Newspaper Articles, Theater Programs, and Yearbook, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Poster, 1972 (Box Shared Fales 116, Folder 7)
- Series II. Journalism and Teaching, 1974-2001; 4.52 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes, 1 large flat box, 1 small flat box, and 2 cassette boxes; 26 audiocassettes; 471 Megabytes in 3 computer files
  This series consists of materials created and collected by Harron during her journalism career. Most of the files cover her writing on punk music and music in general, but there are files related to other cultural topics, such as television and theater. Materials include drafts and manuscripts, interview transcripts, interview recordings, research files, correspondence, and final published versions of Harron's writing for publications including New Statesman, Punk, Melody Maker, and The Guardian. Harron's interview transcripts and recordings of such iconic bands as the Sex Pistols, and her writing for Punk (an early publication that focused on the counterculture) reflect her central role in documenting this emerging category of music. Also included are notes and reading for a course Harron taught on subcultures in 1980.
  Arranged alphabetically by publication or article title.
  - Boulevard -- Draft, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Edinburgh International Television Festival: Messages from the Furniture -- Final Publication, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Equator -- Correspondence and Final Publication, October 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Event -- Final Publication, November 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Forbes ASAP -- Correspondence and Draft, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Guardian -- Draft Reviews, circa 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Independent on Sunday, 1995
    - Final Text (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Interview -- RuPaul (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0111)
  - London Trax -- Final Text, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Marxism Today -- Final Publication, April 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Melody Maker
    - Drafts, Notes, Interview Transcripts, and Final Texts, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 11-12, Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Interviews
      - Gang of Four and Andy Corrigan, 1978 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0129)
      - Luke at Richmond Hostel and Pub in Dalston; Paul at Party in Hoxton, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0097)
      - The Mekons -- Mark White and Andy in the Studio; John and Andy in York, Autumn 1978 (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0059)
      - The Mekons, circa 1978 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0098)
      - Punk Miscellaneous/James Chance and Anya Philips Interview, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0121)
  - National Post -- Drafts, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - National Screw -- Drafts and Research Materials, circa 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - New Musical Express -- Final Text, April 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - New Socialist -- Proofs, circa 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - New Statesman -- Drafts and Final Texts/Publications, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16, Box 4, Folder 1)
  - New Wave Rock -- Draft and Final Publication, November 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Paris Metro -- Drafts, Notes, and Final Text, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 28, Folder 4)
  - "Pop as Commodity" -- Drafts and Research -- Chapter for Facing the Music: A Pantheon Guide to Popular Culture by Simon Firith, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Punk
    - Drafts and Final Texts/Publications, 1976-1977 and 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5, Box 28)
    - Interviews
      - Gayle Advert -- London, October 1977 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0128)
      - Au Pairs, circa 1979-1980 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0102)
      - The Damned -- Stiff Records, undated (Box 30, Audiocassette 608.0058)
      - Eddie and the Hot Rods, 1979; FA_MSS_608_ER_10
      - Mars, 1977 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0075)
      - PiL -- John Lydon and Keith Levene -- Tape 1, 1980 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.008)
      - Skins -- The George/Hammersmith, Tube Station, Hostel in Richman, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0082)
  - Saturday Night -- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Smash Hits -- Final Publication, December 1980-January 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sounds -- Final Text, August 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Sunday Telegraph -- Correspondence, Proof, and Final Texts, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sunday Times -- Drafts and Final Texts, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10, Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Times Educational Supplement -- Proof, July 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Village Voice -- Drafts and Final Texts, 1977 and 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Why the Big Apple Lacks Bite" -- Final Text -- Unidentified Publication, circa 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ZG Magazine -- Final Publication, circa 1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Publications -- Manuscripts, Interview Transcripts, Research Materials, and Notes
    - Punk, Rock and Roll, and Pop, circa 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Rap, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Skinheads and "Oi" Music, circa 1980 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Stoneman Family, 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Various Topics (Including Lindsay Kemp and Teen Magazines), 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - White Russians of Paris, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified Publications -- Interview Recordings
    - Keith Allen, November 12, 1981
      - Tape 1 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0124)
      - Tape 2 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.009)
      - Tape 3, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0116)
    - Marc Almond -- London, May 20, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0089)
    - Kenneth Anger, April 1980
      - NYC (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0077)
      - Tape 1 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0079)
    - Joan Baez, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0078)
    - Garry Bushell, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0083)
    - Dale Cornelius -- Nashville, October 28, 1983 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0101)
    - John Ehrlichman, May 1, 1976 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0086)
    - Amanda Lear/Jimmy Savile, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0088)
    - Mr. Magic, circa 1982 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0115)
    - Maureen Tucker -- Tape 1, September 20, 1985 (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0071)
    - Michael Zilkha, undated (Box 29, Audiocassette 608.0076)
  - Teaching -- St. Martin's College of Art -- Course on Subcultures -- Notes and Research, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Series III. Television, 1984-2006; 4.58 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes and 1 record carton; 10 Betacam_SP; 3 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 53 VHS; 8.75 Gigabytes in 14 computer files
  This series consists of materials related to shows on which Harron worked in some capacity (as a researcher, editorial assistant, or writer) or episodes and television movies she produced or directed. Materials include video recordings, scripts, and cast and crew lists. Notable programs include shows for BBC's Channel 4, Ear Say (the first show on which she worked), Arena (a British documentary series), The Late Show (a British arts program), Edge (an American public television show), South Bank Show (a British arts show), Without Walls (a British show on culture), Big Love, The Nine, and Anna Nicole, a television movie.
  Arranged alphabetically by show or series name.
  - Anna Nicole -- Director's Cut, December 21, 2012; FA_MSS_608_ER_57
  - Arena
    - Buñuel, February 11, 1984 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0153)
    - Catholics -- "How Do You Solve a Problem Like Maria?", March 27, 1987 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0138)
    - Desert Island Discs, undated (Box 32, Vhs 608.0137)
    - Jazz Jukebox, undated (Box 32, Vhs 608.0139)
  - BBC -- Channel 4
    - BBC Press Pass, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Campaign 2, circa 1998 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0149)
    - Raymond Chandler, undated (Box 31, Vhs 608.0012)
    - Katherine Hepburn, undated (Box 31, Vhs 608.0008)
    - Innovation -- Flamenco, undated (Box 32, Vhs 608.014)
    - Palestine/Ten Commandments -- Adam, undated (Box 32, Vhs 608.0141)
    - Saturday Review -- Bornemann, Patrick Hamilton, undated (Box 34, Vhs 608.0159)
  - Big Love -- Episode 106 Director -- Script, Schedules, Crew List, and Floor Plans, May-June 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Agent, 1996; FA_MSS_608_ER_3
  - Ear Say
    - #1, March 31, 1984 (Box 31, Vhs 608.0013)
    - #2-3, April 7-14, 1984 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0142)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Weegee, undated (Box 35, Vhs 608.0042)
  - Edge -- Thirteen/WNET
    - #1, undated
    - #101, October 7, 1991 (Box 33, Vhs 608.0173)
    - #101, undated (Box 34, Vhs 608.0157)
    - #101, undated (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.0052)
    - #103, undated (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.005)
    - Correspondence, circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Late Show
    - #179, September 4, 1990 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0034)
    - #198, May 29, 1991 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0033)
    - #360, October 3, 1991 (Box 34, Vhs 608.0163)
    - American Late Show #6, undated (Box 35, Vhs 608.0039)
    - American Late Show #103, undated (Box 33, Vhs 608.0018)
    - American Late Show #107, undated (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.0051)
    - American Late Show -- "Trouble in Paradise", undated (Box 36, Vhs 608.0036)
    - "Batman", May 15, 1989 (Box 31, Vhs 608.0006)
    - "Black Widow", March 4, 1989 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0135)
    - "Brixton to Barbados", undated (Box 32, Vhs 608.0136)
    - "Edinburgh Nights", undated
      - Porn 68A -- Jukebox Music (Box 35, Betacam sp 608.0044)
      - Porn 69A (Box 35, Betacam sp 608.0177)
      - Pornography -- 3rd Cut, Conformed (Box 35, Betacam sp 608.0045)
    - "Fakes", undated
      - 19 -- Gombrich (Box 31, Vhs 608.0009)
      - Books #2 (Box 33, Vhs 608.0151)
      - Mrs 07429 (Box 31, Vhs 608.001)
    - Albert Goldman -- Episode Directed by Harron, April-June 1992
      - Albert Goldman/James Wolcott (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.0053)
      - Sound Roll #1 (Box 37, Half inch video reel 608.0055)
      - Sound Roll #2 (Box 37, Half inch video reel 608.0056)
      - Sound Roll #3 (Box 37, Half inch video reel 608.0057)
    - Inauguration Programme -- Schedule, Transcripts, and Footage Information, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9-11)
    - "Late Again", March 11, 1990 (Box 35, Vhs 608.0038)
    - "Liverpool/Leningrad", February 28, 1989
      - Tapes 14-15 (Box 34, Vhs 608.0156)
      - Translator's Copy (Box 31, Vhs 608.0016)
      - TX (Box 34, Vhs 608.0165)
    - "PasB", September 20, 1989 (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.0049)
    - "The Press", June 24, 1987 (Box 34, Vhs 608.0158)
    - Review, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - "Times Square", August 11, 1989
      - Kenneth Anger #1 (Box 36, Vhs 608.0032)
      - Dub (Box 31, Vhs 608.0004)
      - History of Times Square -- 1 of 2 (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.0047)
      - History of Times Square -- 1 of 2 (Box 37, Betacam sp 608.0048)
      - Interview Transcripts, Research Material, and Legs McNeil's "Last Days of Times Square" Manuscript (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - TX (Box 34, Vhs 608.0161)
      - Video Recording (Box 31, Vhs 608.0015)
      - Video Recording (Box 33, Vhs 608.015)
      - Video Recording (Box 33, Vhs 608.0174)
      - Video Recording (Box 35, Vhs 608.004)
      - Video Recording (Box 35, Vhs 608.0041)
    - "Tories", September 12, 1987 (Box 33, Vhs 608.0172)
    - "Vengeance", July 8, 1987 (Box 32, Vhs 608.0148)
    - Whitbread Prize, January 24, 1989 (Box 31, Vhs 608.0007)
  - The Nine
    - Episode 8 Director -- Series "Bible", Scripts, Location Outline, and Call Sheet, September-October 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Episode "Brother's Keeper" -- Network Cut 2, September 27, 2006; FA_MSS_608_ER_55
    - Episode "Heroes Welcome" -- Final Locked Avid, September 25, 2006; FA_MSS_608_ER_56
  - Pasadena -- Episode 106 Director-- Crew List, Editor's Cut, and Concept, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Punk Rock in the 70s" Segment Transcript -- Unidentified Show, 2000; FA_MSS_608_ER_4
  - Six Degrees -- Episode 106 Director -- Crew List, Beat Sheet, and Schedule, August-September 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - South Bank Show
    - Marguerite Duras, undated
      - Photograph (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Video Recording (Box 34, Vhs 608.0164)
    - General -- Schedule and Photographs, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - King Lear
      - Stage History and Episode Outline, circa 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Video Recording, undated (Box 34, Vhs 608.0169)
    - Nico and John Cale -- Transcripts, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Jackson Pollock
      - Shot List and Transcripts, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
      - Video Recording, October 2, 1988 (Box 33, Vhs 608.0175)
      - Video Recording, circa 1988 (Box 34, Vhs 608.0162)
    - Andy Warhol, May 18, 1988 (Box 34, Vhs 608.0168)
    - Wooster Group
      - Photographs, Memo, and Poster, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Route 1 and 9 -- Brussels -- Masters, circa 1987 (Box 33, Vhs 608.0171)
      - Video Recording, February 12, 1987 (Box 34, Vhs 608.017)
  - Without Walls: The Thing Is... with Paul Morley, April 1991
    - Interview -- Final (Box 34, Vhs 608.0166)
    - Reviews (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Video Recording (Box 35, Vhs 608.0037)
- Series IV. Film, 1939-2018; 13.48 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes, 2 cassette boxes, 1 small flat box, 1 large flat box, and 1 record carton; 19 audiocassettes; 17 VHS; 1 Video8; 1 U-matic; 21.86 Gigabytes in 556 computer files
  This series consists of materials related to Harron's feature films, shorts, and documentaries. Materials include video and audio recordings (both digital and analog), shoot photographs, cast and crew lists, contracts, set and production binders, shoot schedules, correspondence, reviews, screening and film festival materials (such as premiere invitations and festival programs), budgets, scene lists, scripts, and research materials (articles, archival photocopies, and publications).
  Arranged alphabetically into five subseries and alphanumerically within each one.
  - Subseries IV.A. I Shot Andy Warhol, 1954-1997; 5.48 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes, 1 cassette box, 1 small flat box, and 1 large flat box; 2 audiocassettes; 3 VHS; 23.13 Megabytes in 24 computer files